If you upset her
I'll throw you in the river to feed the fish
Yes
Boss Kyle
Ms. Zoe
I was blind to your greatness
Three days it is
You're lucky, kid
Those damn scumbags
You'll rot in hell
Shut up
Hurry and figure out how to
get the formula within three days
Or I'm a dead man
What's there to think about
Isn't the formula with Lewes
Just have him hand it over
Exactly
Just make him bring it out
I'm his mother
Give me a break
When we tried to borrow money from him before
did he give a single cent
He
He never treats us like family
Lewes
Cynthia
Get the hell out here
Mom, Dad
What happened to you
I'm drowning in loan shark debt
The house was seized too
I'm completely broke
Sis
From now on, Mom and Dad
are yours to support